<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GapQuiz</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_gap">AboutGap</string>
    <string name="aboutGapQuiz">
        About Gap Quiz
    </string>

    <string name="Paragraph1">
        This quiz has been developed to allow you to test your understanding of a wide range of
        issues relating to Good Academic Practice. In particular the quiz allows you to demonstrate
        your awareness of:
    </string>
    <string name="Paragraph2">
        &#8226;what is meant by the term plagiarism \n
        &#8226;what is deemed to be acceptable and unacceptable academic practice \n
        &#8226;how to correctly cite and reference different source material \n
        &#8226;how good academic practice, including different learning strategies and study skills,
        can help you to avoid plagiarising other people’s work and so become an effective learner.
    </string>
    <string name="paragraph3">
        The questions are all at an introductory level, which means they are suitable for anyone
        studying at higher education level. You may find it useful to repeat the quiz at key points
        in your studies (e.g. before you submit each piece of coursework).
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_start_quiz">StartQuiz</string>

    <string name="quizIntroTitle">
        INTRODUCTORY LEVEL: GOOD ACADEMIC PRACTICE QUIZ
    </string>

    <string name="quizIntro">
        There is no limit to the number of times you can attempt this quiz and you will find that
        the questions change each time you try it. You must leave a gap of a week between each
        attempt at the quiz. \n
        You should submit your answer to each question and read the feedback provided before moving
        on to the next question. As you complete each question, a coloured bar will appear.
        Correct answers are shown by a green bar, partially correct answers by an amber bar and
        incorrect answers by a red bar.\n

        You can have multiple attempts at some questions, but you will lose marks for each attempt
        at a question that is incorrect.\n

        Use the \'Next\' link at the bottom of each question to move to the next question. When you
        have completed the quiz, click \'Submit all and finish\' in order to receive your score and
        review your answers.
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_question1">
        This is an introductory level question on \'Collaboration versus collusion\'.
    </string>

    <string name="question1Instruction">
        Read the following definitions and decide whether they are descriptions of collaboration
        or collusion. (Select the appropriate term from the drop-down list.)
    </string>

    <string name="question1a">
        Working closely with one or more students to allow you all to practise and develop your
        understanding of a particular topic or skill
    </string>

    <string name="question1b">
        Working closely with one or more students to personally gain or give someone else an unfair
        advantage over other students
    </string>

    <string name="question1c">
        Asking another student to help you with the specific answer to an assignment question
    </string>

    <string name="question1d">
        Joining a study group in which you discuss different aspects of the course and how to
        approach tasks within the assignments
    </string>

    <string name="question1e">
        Posting the exact course references needed to answer an assignment task on the course forum
    </string>


    <string name="Q2Intro">
        This is an introductory level question on \'Common knowledge\'.
    </string>
    <string name="Q2Instruct">
        Read the following statement and decide whether it is true or false.
    </string>
    <string name="Q2">
        For one of your assignment questions you need to summarise some group work from an online
        activity. You decide to include a few select quotes from messages posted to the course
        forum from different students. As these messages are all public (as far as the course is
        concerned), they represent common knowledge, so do not need to be referenced.\n

        Select one:
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_question2">Question2</string>

    <string name="Q3">
        You do not need to reference information that is recognised as common knowledge within a
        specific subject area. \n
        Select one:
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_question3">Question3</string>

    <string name="source">
        This question was designed by Coventry University.
    </string>
    <string name="Q4Intro">
        This is an introductory level question on \‘Citing and referencing\’.
    </string>
    <string name="Q4Instruct">
        In general, academics and students in the United Kingdom use a range of styles for citing
        and referencing the work of other people in their academic writing.
    </string>
    <string name="Q4">
        Coventry University has developed a policy that all students of the University should
        follow when writing in-text citations and the List of References for their assignments.
        Which one of the following options describes the policy at Coventry University?
        \n Select one:
    </string>
    <string name="optionAQ4">
        a. You must always use the conventions described in the Coventry University Harvard
        Reference Style Guide
    </string>
    <string name="optionBQ4">
        b. You can make up your own style for citing and referencing
    </string>
    <string name="optionCQ4">
        c. You should use the conventions described in the Coventry University Harvard Reference
        Style Guide, unless your Module tutor requires you to use an alternative style
    </string>
    <string name="optionDQ4">
       d. You must use a recognised style, but you can use a mixture of styles within an assignment
    </string>
    <string name="optionEQ4">
        e. As long as you use an automated referencing system, such as RefWorks, the style does not
        matter Incorrect
    </string>

    <string name="sourceQ5">
        Colin Neville, The Complete Guide to Referencing and Avoiding Plagiarism, Ó 2007,
        Reproduced with the kind permission of Open University Press.  All rights reserved.
    </string>
    <string name="Q5Instruct">
        To test your understanding of when to cite and reference, look at the following situations
        that can occur when writing assignments.
    </string>
    <string name="Q5">
        Which ones require an in-text citation and an entry in the List of References?
    </string>
    <string name="optionAQ5">
        a. When stating or summarising common knowledge or obvious facts, and when there is unlikely
        to be any significant disagreement with your statements or summaries.
    </string>
    <string name="optionBQ5">
        b. When you include tables, photographs, statistics and diagrams, produced by other authors,
        in your assignment.
    </string>
    <string name="optionCQ5">
        c. To give weight or credibility to an argument.
    </string>
    <string name="optionDQ5">
        d. When paraphrasing or summarising (in your own words) another person’s work that you feel
        is particularly significant, or likely to be a subject of debate.
    </string>

    <string name="Q6">
        Statement: To indicate that a section of your writing contains a short quotation taken from
        another source, you should place it in quotation marks, insert an in-text citation at the
        end of the quotation, for example, (Fowler 2008: 45), and include the full reference at the
        end of your coursework.\n
        Select one:
    </string>

    <string name="Q7Intro">
        This is an introductory level question on ‘Why students plagiarise’.
    </string>
     <string name="Q7Instruct">
       Select one from the scenarios below.
    </string>
    <string name="Q7">
        In which of the following scenarios might it be valid for a student to use the work (words,
        ideas, images, data etc.) of other people without acknowledging the original source?\n
        Select one:
    </string>
    <string name="optAQ7">
        a. The student has run out of time to complete the coursework properly
    </string>
    <string name="optBQ7">
        b. The student believes that paraphrasing an expert’s words would be too difficult as well
        as disrespectful
    </string>
    <string name="optCQ7">
        c. Another student has given the student a copy of their work before the deadline. The
        student copies it and submits it as his or her own coursework
    </string>
    <string name="optDQ7">
        d. The student does not understand how to cite and reference
    </string>
    <string name="optEQ7">
        e. The student knows that essays can be purchased on the Internet and that other students
        are buying and using them. S/he decides to submit a purchased essay
    </string>
    <string name="optFQ7">
        f. None of the above reasons are valid
    </string>

    <string name="Q8Instruct">
        Select all that apply.
    </string>
    <string name="Q8">
        Which of the following approaches can help a student avoid plagiarising other materials?\n
        Select one more
    </string>
    <string name="optAQ8">
         a. Developing good note-taking skills
    </string>
    <string name="optBQ8">
        b. Making notes in your own words rather than copying directly from source materials
    </string>
    <string name="optCQ8">
        c. Not discussing the exact answers to questions with other students
    </string>
    <string name="optDQ8">
        d. Clearly separating directly copied phrases or sentences from a source, by placing them
        in \'quotation marks\' and adding an in-text citation immediately afterwards
    </string>
    <string name="optEQ8">
        e. Cutting and pasting information from different sources into your answer, which you plan 
        to rephrase later
    </string>

    <string name="Q9Intro">
        This is an introductory level question on \'What is good academic practice?\'
    </string>
    <string name="Q9Instruct">
        Read the following scenario:
    </string>
    <string name="Q9">
        <b>Scenario</b>: A student is struggling with some of the questions in his next assignment,
        so decides to post each question on a study chat site he\'s found useful in the past when
        he\'s needed information on a wide range of topics.\n

        The next day, three responses have been posted to one question along with two answers to
        the other two questions. He chooses what he thinks are the best responses for each question,
        and pastes them directly into his assignment to create his final assignment answers. \n

        This scenario is an example of <i>good academic practice</i>.Is this statement true or false?\n

        Select one:
    </string>

    <string name="Q10Instruct">
        From the descriptions below, tap and drop the appropriate word that matches each.
    </string>
    <string name="Q10A">
        Working appropriately with one or more students to help you practise and develop your
        understanding.
    </string>
    <string name="Q10B">
        Something that is widely known within your subject area and can be attributed to a number
        of sources
    </string>
    <string name="Q10C">
        Presenting someone else\'s words or ideas (intentionally or not) as your own work in order
        to gain personal benefit.
    </string>
    <string name="Q10D">
        Working inappropriately with one or more students to gain or give an unfair advantage, e.g.
        jointly answering assignment questions rather than working individually.
    </string>
    <string name="Q10E">
        Providing the full details (author, title, etc.) of the source material used in your work,
        normally presented as a list at the end of your coursework
    </string>
    <string-array name="opt1">
        <item>Select one...</item>
        <item>Collaboration</item>
        <item>Collusion</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_question11"></string>
    <string name="Q11Instruct">
        Select one or more:
    </string>
    <string name="Q11">
        Which of the following options are examples of unacceptable collusion? (Select all that
        apply.) \n
    </string>
    <string name="Q11A">
        a. Sending your final answers to a friend who has fallen behind with their studies and
        needs some tips on how to complete the assignment
    </string>
    <string name="Q11B">
        b. Deciding to jointly write up a group activity with the other members of the group even
        though you have been told to do this individually
    </string>
    <string name="Q11C">
        c. Asking a friend who did the course last year to proofread your assignment and then
        incorporating all the changes and additions they have made
    </string>
    <string name="Q11D">
        d. Discussing general approaches to answering an assignment question with one or more
        students, but without describing the actual answer
    </string>
    <string name="Q11E">
        e. Directing another student to appropriate sections in the course books that should help
        them when completing the next assignment
    </string>
    <string name="Q11F">
        f. Asking another student for some general advice and guidance on how to approach an
        assignment question
    </string>
    <string name="Q11G">
        g. Downloading another person’s marked assignment from a social networking space, and using 
        their answers and feedback to construct your own answer
    </string>

    <string name="Q12Intro">
        This is an introductory level question on /‘Understanding Turnitin/’
    </string>
    <string name="aboutTurnitin">
        You may be instructed by your Module tutor to submit your coursework online and, if so, you
        will be required to submit your work into a system called Turnitin. \n
        Turnitin compares the text of your coursework with a variety of online sources.\n

        It produces a report that details the extent to which the text of your coursework has been
        matched to your own and other people’s previously submitted or published work.
    </string>
    <string name="Q12">
        <b>Scenario</b>: A student has plagiarised material from a variety of sources, as he does
        not believe that the University will find out.  He submits a draft version of his
        coursework to Turnitin.\n

        Which of the following sources of material do you think Turnitin will compare his work with?
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptA">
       a. Web sites
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptB">
      b. His previously submitted work (final versions)
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptC">
        c. E-books
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptD">
       d. Online academic and professional journals
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptE">
        e. Work submitted by other University students
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptF">
        f. Student essay banks
    </string>
    <string name="Q12OptG">
        g. His previously submitted work (draft)
    </string>

    <string name="Q13OptA">
        a. When pulling together a range of key ideas that you introduced and referenced earlier in
        the assignment.
    </string>
    <string name="Q13OptB">
        b. When including quotations.
    </string>
    <string name="Q13OptC">
        c. When describing or discussing a theory, model or practice associated with a particular
        author.
    </string>
    <string name="stringD">
        c. When you are discussing your own ideas, reflections or research findings.
    </string>

    <string name="Q14Intro">
        This is an introductory level question on ‘Writing in your own words’.
    </string>
    <string name="Q14Instruct">
        In this question you will be asked to read an extract from an academic source, followed by
        an example of a student’s essay in which they have attempted to paraphrase the original
        academic source. You are to decide whether or not the student has paraphrased the original
        source in an acceptable manner, as well as followed the correct conventions for citing and
        referencing it.
    </string>
    <string name="Q14A">
        Paraphrasing means to put the original source into your own words.  It is an important
        skill to develop as it demonstrates that you have understood, rather than simply reproduced,
        what you have read.\n
        The original extract is from an article by Dr. Erik Borg published in The Academic Writer,
        the journal of The Centre for Academic Writing, Coventry University,
    </string>
    <string name="Q14Extract">
        Academic integrity refers to a code of behaviour that is expected of all participants in
        academic life.  Based on the fundamental value of honesty, the expectations associated with
        academic integrity are not different from those of life outside the academy, and among them
        are that participants will not cheat, plagiarise, improperly collude, or falsify research
        findings. \n

        Plagiarism is the use of other people\’s language and ideas without appropriate credit.
        Plagiarism is one of the most challenging areas of academic integrity.  \n
        (Borg 2010: 1).
    </string>
    <string name="Q14Reference">
        List of References \n
        Borg, E. (2010) \‘What is academic integrity?\’ The Academic Writer 1 (1), 1-2
    </string>
    <string name="Q14Paraphrased">
   <b> Consider the following extract from a student\’s essay:</b>
        According to Borg, academics need to uphold the values associated with integrity within the
        scholarly community, in much the same way as they would in their everyday lives (2010: 1).
        Although he refers to a range of academic crimes, in particular Borg argues that academics
        should not plagiarise and that plagiarism is a highly complex issue (2010: 1).
        The complicated nature of plagiarism will now be discussed in more detail. \n

        List of References

        Borg, E. (2010) \‘What is academic integrity?\’  The Academic Writer 1 (1), 1-2
    </string>
    <string name="Q14B">
        <b>Is this statement true or false?  The student has paraphrased the original source in an
        acceptable manner and correctly followed the conventions for citing and referencing.</b>
    </string>
    <string-array name="Tutorials">
        <item>Plagiarism and its forms</item>
        <item>Collusion versus collaboration</item>
        <item>Referencing and Citation</item>
        <item>Common Knowledge</item>
        <item>TurnitIn</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_tutorials">Tutorials</string>
    <string name="register_for_quiz_button">REGISTER FOR QUIZ</string>
</resources>
 


    